Promise, Chiara and I will really
work hard and practice
for our very special first dance.
-Let's see it!
-Yeah.
So cute!
I thought you were my friend.
I thought you always stood
for what was right.
I was wrong.
How can we be sure it's really Quintin?
There are other senators, right?
It's just strange, sweetheart.
I mean, I'm not exactly stiff
when I dance.
I can shake my hips and groove just fine.
But I don't know.
When it comes to couple dancing,
I just lose all my confidence.
I don't know why.
Come here, Mikoy.
I'll teach you how to dance.
No, your right!
Hand on her waist.
There you go! With feelings.
That's right. Right.
Come on, you two.
Stop butting in.
This is for couples only.
Oh, come on. Cut it out.
-Let's continue.
-Hey!
Sorry about them, Chiara.
They're just excited.
It's okay.
You'd better get used to it.
It's not every day
a family member gets married.
How about you? Are you excited?
I am.
I'm just not used to this.
It's not like this back in Prague.
People are more formal,
more intimate,
and more reserved.
Here, it feels like
the whole town is getting married.
You know, that's just how it is
here in the Philippines.
When one person is happy,
everyone celebrates,
and when one person has a problem,
everyone shares the burden.
You're still not used to it?
I'm just not used
to so many people preparing
and celebrating for us.
You know, you'd better get used to it
because you're family now.
And in this family, no one prepares alone.
Thank you, Mommy Tess.
Thank you for welcoming me with open arms.
Tess!
That's Paula.
Looks like she's got some gossip.
-I'll go talk to her.
-Sure.
What is it?
-She always calls here.
-I wonder why.
Where am I?
Do you know him?
Yes.
What do you mean, yes?
Yes, he's my patient.
What's his illness?
I can't tell you.
And why not?
Don't you know who we are?
Don't you know
what we're capable of doing to you?
I won't break
my oath as a doctor.
Even if you tie me up, or even kill me.
Chiara.
I want to show you something.
Is this you?
No.
Are you sure?
It really isn't me, Mario.
Please believe me.
If it's not you,
then who is she?
The doctor is a man of principle.
All right, Doc.
Let's put those principles to the test.
What's that?
It's my squishy toy. Keep it down.
I squeeze it when I'm anxious.
I'm not afraid of you.
It's like he knows we won't hurt him.
Like he knows we're good people now,
and we've turned over a new leaf.
He knows we're bluffing.
What do we do now?
If we can't torture him,
maybe you could rough him up,
just a little.
Easy there, partner.
We might end up back in prison.
That would ruin your blossoming romance
with Agent Sianong.
True.
Being a good person is hard.
What are you doing?
Yo, yo, yo
Doc with the funky smell
Confidential or essential, spill it now!
Our patience is running out somehow!
Cool, calm, and collected? Not today
Drop the bomb, drop the truth
While you're at it
Drop that wisdom tooth!
That's enough!
This is worse than torture!
Do whatever you want. Just stop rapping!
That was just the intro, Doc.
Who’s that?
Uncle Mario.
Can I post this?
It's great content.
I'm sure it'll go viral.
It'll be trending.
Right?
Sure.
Who knows? Someone might recognize them.
Or if not, they'll recognize me.
-Yo!
-I'll go viral.
I'll gain more followers.
Oh, Rahmboy. Not everything
has to be posted.
This is an investigation.
If this gets out,
it'll be much harder to find out
who this dangerous person really is.
The one with Manananggal blood.
Mikoy's right.
We can't let this slide.
Uh, Uncle Mario…
Mikoy. Chiara.
What?
I know now.
I have a suspect.
Who?
-This is unbelievable.
-Who?
There!
Who is it?
-Who?
-There! That's the one!
-Agent Alex?
Agent Alex.
Is this you?
They're pointing at you.
They say you're the suspect.
You're the only "Agent Alex"
who's new around here.
And the birds said…
-What birds?
-Us? Birds?
They said you're good at fighting.
Of course! It's Alex!
She's really good!
Possible, possible.
It's also possible you're a Manananggal.
Manan…
Confess already. You're busted.
Yes. Wait. What are you
even talking about?
Guys, leave Alex alone.
It's not her.
Mikoy, how can you be so sure?
First, they're different heights.
Second, Alex has way better posture.
You're sure that's not me, right?
Enough.
This isn't a guessing game.
It's an investigation.
Agent Alex.
What do you have to say
about the allegations
that you're the mysterious vigilante?
There!
Rahmboy.
Follow-up question. Do you have a twin?
Or maybe a split personality?
Or do you transform at midnight?
That's it!
Uncle Mario.
Can I arrest them now?
-Mario.
-Uncle Mario.
-Go ahead!
-We were just kidding!
-Absolutely.
-You're in trouble!
Absolutely.
Mario, she can't possibly
be a Manananggal.
She's way too pretty!
-We've missed you.
-Oh, there.
The one beside you. That's her.
Alex!
Seriously!
Promise you'll tell us
The truth and nothing but the truth?
-Okay.
-No more, no less
Or you'll lose your teeth!
Fine!
Piece of cake!
You've got it all wrong.
The truth is, the senator isn't sick.
What he has…
is a dream.
The truth is,
he's just trying to regrow his hair.
There!
What happened?
I paid in full.
Why did only half of it grow back?
Unfortunately, the medicine
isn't perfect yet.
I've got bangs. On just one side.
But you're right.
Because I know his dream
of having a full head of hair,
and he trusts me
with his other dreams as well.
And with his deepest secrets.
What?
Why did you make a move on Moraviano?
It's not time yet.
Enough. You've done enough.
If you can't clean this up,
you'd better pack your things too.
I'm sorry, Senator,
but it's still not working.
That's all right.
It doesn't have to be perfect.
You know, let them think
that we're shedding hair and going bald.
Meanwhile, we stay quiet
and rise when they're not looking.
Stronger,
more powerful,
and more disciplined.
Until nothing can stop us.
I thought all he wanted back was his hair.
Turns out it's the Sinigang Cartel 2.0.
I'm sorry about what happened.
It shouldn't have come to that.
The guards who did that to you
have been taken off duty,
and I've returned
your entire Chilimansi stash.
Complete.
Thank you.
But that's not the only reason I'm here.
Someone wants to meet you.
Who?
Someone with many connections
and great influence.
Someone who can offer you more
than just Chilimansi.
Every flavor.
Every single flavor, Viktor.
He can give you all of them.
Are you here?
Are you following me?
This is too much, Sir Viktor.
We’re already trapped here,
and they still want
to make a deal with you.
Such long hair you have!
What did they want?
But it seems like
we will find out very soon.
Mr. Valtrovi.
I’m just following orders.
What?
It’s okay.
What? Should we tell Agent Sianong?
Not yet.
-He just had crispy pork lunch.
-Huh?!
He might get high blood.
He had crispy pork?
He didn’t even invite me.
Meanwhile, I was always cooking
for him at the safehouse.
Now that he has a girlfriend,
he's forgotten all about me.
Let’s say I’m not good with secrets.
What secret is that?
Well then, how much
crispy pork have you eaten?
Agent Alex!
Mikoy.
Are you sure
that’s not you?
Earlier, you were on my side,
and now you’re asking me.
That’s not really you.
I’m getting nervous.
Why?
I’m not the same waiter
you met in Prague, Alex.
I’ve learned so many things.
Why? What’s your theory?
La Morte Bianca is gone,
but not the Concordat.
Agent Alex, if someone followed us here,
I want to know as soon as possible,
before everything gets ruined.
Alex, I just want to get married.
To start a new normal life.
Our life is okay here.
Peaceful.
I don’t want anyone to ruin it.
You might not be admitting it,
but you are still able to retain
your insticts as an asset.
Sianong will be happy about it.
I’ll see what I can do about this.
Thank you.
What did you do to him?
You kidnapped, tortured,
and abducted him. What is this?
Technically, nothing yet.
You’re right about the kidnapped,
but we just let him sit, that’s all.
We didn’t hurt him.
That’s true.
But please,
make him stop with his rapping.
Ouch, Doc!
Just tell us the truth or else…
Fine. I’ll tell you the truth.
Okay, Doc, tell the whole truth
to Agent Sianong.
I will spill everything.
About senator Quintin.
This way.
Viktor Valtrovi!
All right, Sen.
CAFE ALLOR
RISTORANTE
Suru.
Agent Alex?
What did you need?
I have someone
you have to background check.
Okay, who?
All the people here in Mikoy’s house.
All?
Everyone.
From Captain Pepe to Rahmboy.
Thank you.
Let’s see who amongst them
is the real vigilant.
No one should find out about this.
Is that clear?
Understood, sir.
The person we are monitoring
is not just a simple Senator,
but a new syndicate
that is about to be born.
You are powerful enough
to take me outside,
but you can’t make my case disappear?
I can’t do that.
But I can make something else disappear.
You.
Since when are you taking
action without me knowing?
Since when have you and Cocoy
been independently investigating
Senator Quintin?
I can’t erase from my mind
that CCTV that Daddy Mario showed.
Forget about it.
Sweetheart, that person
is not just someone else.
It seems like that person
has the same moves as me and Donatelo.
I'm starting to think we might have been
at the same training in Sicily.